4x10 - Snow Job
Transcript: Anyone/Tomvigfr
Synchro: Anyone/Sixe
www.swsub.com
I'm asking if you think
I should work with this girl.
I'm asking if you can work with her
without trying to bang her.
- She has a boyfriend!
- I don't think you could work with her
- without trying to bang her.
- I never seem to be able to.
But the girl you work with
wanna bang you, doesn't she?
- Wait still that she does he.
- She has a boyfriend!
So? It's not a husband!
And if you think she'd wanna bang you
if she didn't have a boyfriend,
you'd lie and wait.
Eventually, that would end,
- you'd be in like Flynn.
- Totally!
Is that why you guys never get laid,
always waiting for a relationship stand?
E., last night, you thought
you were on a date with the girl.
I'm not sure you can let that go
and be professional.
- Well, I am sure.
- Then when are you asking?
I'm just making sure you're OK with it.
Are you OK with it?
Not all clients are as easy as me.
And actresses...?
- Forget it!
- Oh, yeah!
The girl's in town, alright?
It's a great way to expend our business.
- Our business?
- Yeah.
I've been thinking.
You and I 50/50 on every client I hit.
- When do I fit in?
- You don't.
You know, that's sweet,
but not necessary.
Look, I know where I'd be without you!
Nowhere!
Don't you have a job to go to, Drama?
That's the beauty of an ensemble cast!
It's who they work with.
E., it is not necessary.
Great! There're other people
who're recognizing what you do for me,
and I wish you nothing but success.
I only ask that you make sure
that my career attention
does not suffer.
Yeah, E. Look after Numero uno.
Always, always, always!
I have Dana Gordon.
Weird ! I used to push up
on top of Dana Gordon like this!
True story.
Dana! I was just thinking about you!
Did you read Billy Walsh's script?
Did I get Billy Walsh's script?
I got it this morning.
- Do I have Billy Walsh's script?
- No, I've just brought it out.
Call Walsh and find out
why I didn't have a chance
to comment on it before he turned it in.
Just got it! How's it feeling?
I'm on page 12 and I do not understand
what I'm reading.
You didn't understand Titanic
after 12 pages either, Dana.
Ari? This is totally fucked, OK?
- And this is not what we bought.
- What do you mean?
Read the thing, Ari!
I left a word for Walsh.
Keep trying him! Call E. and make sure
that Vince is reading this as well!
I can't hear you, Lloyd!
I'm in the Hills!
Did you get the Billy Walsh's script?
Lloyd, I can't hear you!
Did you get...
the Billy Walsh's...
- script!
- Shut the fuck up, Lloyd!
No cell reception up here.
Yeah, I got that. Do you have
a hardline here by chance?
- I don't know.
- Thanks, man.
- Here's my guy!
- Hey!
- How are you?
- So, Vince is OK with this?
- Yeah, he was totally cool.
Smart move! I would have
fought him for you,
- I'm a freaky sister on you.
- I'm glad it didn't come to that.
Me too. I'm sorry
for putting you to work day one.
It's just I've got to summon up
my inner supermodel.
I got these people coming at me
with concepts, interviews, wardrobe...
I'm so thankful you're here to help!
I'm glad to do it.
Fashion isn't my thing,
but if you really want my opinion,
I liked the black outfit
you wore on your 1st scary movie.
Made you look smart, some kind of hot.
- You remember that?
- Yeah, it was on...
It's a cable like... a year ago.
And I... I might have bought the DVD.
Watch it just turn it. My job, you know.
Right.
We are gonna be great together,
E. Really great.
- I'm so excited!
- Me too!
What'up, girl?
- Hey, Dave!
- Hey, baby!
This the guy I was telling you about, E.
- This is my boyfriend, Dave.
- Hey, Dave. How are you?
- You're the new manager, Dog?
- Yeah!
I... thought you'd be a little older.
I'm older than I look.
Alright.
- So!
- So...
So, why don't you ask the new manager
what he thinks of my idea?
Dave, I...
What? Yo, check this, OK?
I want them to shoot Anna
in a series of animal poses, OK?
Like when she sticks her neck up
like this, alright? It's like a girafe.
Alright? In another one,
we would make her hair really big,
to be like a lion.
- What do you think?
- That's interesting...
What do you really think?
I think it's a little weird.
No offense, Dave, but... it is.
It is a little weird, Dave.
Well, I thought it'd be hot.
You think everything I do is hot,
and that's why I love you.
But this is a little weird,
so let's let it go, please.
I'm gonna go get ready.
Yo, Dog.
I'm gonna watch my girl get ready, OK?
So, why don't you grab me a coke,
and bring it over to the trailer?
Alright? Yeah. They're right there.
Thanks, Dog.
I'll bring that right over.
- Yeah?
- Hello?
- Hey, Ari what's up?
- What's up, Lloyd?
- I'm looking for Vince.
- Do you know where's Vince?
Aren't you supposed
to go through E for Vince?
- You try E.?
- If he's here, put him on the phone!
I called E. and e-mailed him too.
- I'll see if he's here.
- I'll see if I can locate him.
- Vince, you hear of Ari?
- Why wouldn't I be?
Lloyd says he can't find E.
It's fine.
- Hey, Lloyd!
- Hey, Vince. Hold for Ari.
- Okay.
- I got Ari, Vince.
- Alright.
- Ari!
- I got Vince!
- I got fucking Vince!
- Vince!
- Ari!
- Did you read Walsh's script?
- Did I get Walsh's script?
Well, it was dropped off to me
in the studio this morning.
Any scripts come for us this morning?
Yeah, I put them on the pile.
Yeah, I got it. What's the problem?
The problem is he took
your snow on a mountain movie
and turned it
into a futuristic thriller,
set on a farm, circa 2075!
- I don't understand.
- He tossed the book away!
The book they paid him $3m to write,
and decided just to make up
his own story.
That's odd.
Call Walsh.
Dana Gordon on one.
Did E. know anythin about this?
- Of course, not.
- Then why is he in hiding?
He's not. He's at a photo shoot
with his new client.
E.'s got a new client?
Yeah, Anna Farris.
Come on!
Jesus! The world is falling apart!
It's always darkest before dawn, Ari.
I got Billy's voice mail.
Billy Walsh just said
in response to your question
why did he give the script to the studio
before you had a chance to comment
on it, and I'm quoting him:
"Because I don't give a fuck
what you think."
Get his address.
Sit tight, I will get right back to you.
Bye, Ari.
- Boy, he's stressed!
- You want me to call E.?
No, I'm the producer, I can handle it.
Let's just see what crazy Billy did.
- How about I read this copy?
- Yeah, I like the initiative, Turtle.
What should I do?
Why don't you make us a snack?
I like being E.
Hot, so hot!
Perfect!
Run into it!
You can get a signal
right at the bottom of the hill.
Or we have a runner.
We could send him make the call.
No, thanks.
I'll go down to call.
- Thanks, I appreciate.
- No problem!
- She looks good, huh?
- No, I'm not feeling a shit at all.
Baby?
Do it like a cat, OK?
Ears cats.
Just jump out.
Baby, trust me on this OK? Please?
Hey guys, like an hour,
and this shit is gonna pop.
Come on, Dave...
OK, am I wrong, dog?
Little reckless abandon in here
It'll stand this thing unique.
I think she looks beautiful.
Fucking hack!
Are you cool if I ran down
the bottom of the hill to make a call?
- Yeah.
- OK, I'll be right back.
Alright, everyone. Let's take five.
Alright, sir.
It's Eric, right?
- Yeah!
- You can't leave now.
- Why not?
- I didn't get what I need out of Anna.
She's not focused.
Alright. I'll talk to her.
No, she's not the problem.
The boyfriend is.
As long as he's hanging around
critisizing her,
she's not gonna bring it.
- You wanna say something to him?
- I take pictures.
I don't interfere with domesticity.
Alright. I'll say something to him.
Don't touch the camera.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Listen...
I think you're making Anna
a little uncomfortable.
You've been working with her... what?
One day?
How do you know?
Maybe you're making
the photographer uncomfortable.
if you hang around,
try to be a little less critical.
No, this is not good, OK?
I'm not feeling this.
Anna, baby?
I need to talk to you for a second.
In the trailer.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
Is Billy Walsh here?
No, Billy's not here.
I see him sitting on the couch there.
She means I'm not here for you Ari.
Can I please come in.
Not if you gonna critizise me.
Critizise...
Why would I critizise you?
Let him in.
So everyone hates this script.
You got paid a half a million dollars
to adapt the book and you didn't do it.
Decided to go on a different direction.
They didn't pay you for that direction.
The script that he wrote
is really hot, man.
You don't want to give the studio back
their money, do you?
- The money's been spent.
- On what?
- Home improvements.
- We put in a steam shower
How long will it take you
to do what they paid you to do?
Infinity, cause I'm not gonna do it.
You have to do it.
I tried to do it Ari,
I did, but everytime
I started to write a scene,
I got these 2 guys locked alone
on a moutain and it felt really gay.
And it was my idea to add the chicks.
See, Billy raises chicks really good
Thanks baby.
Vince stops his neckout for you
and now you are fucking him.
And the studio.
- They are going to fuck you right back.
- They can't touch me.
They can sue you and make sure
that you never make a movie
in this town again.
Well good thing I paint.
You are not gonna do this, are you?
No, I'm not.
Then I got nothing else to say to you.
Yeah well,
I got something to say to you:
you are no longer my agent!
- It's your wife, she says it's urgent.
- Put her through Lloyd.
- Here she is.
- What's wrong baby?
You're avoiding my fucking calls.
Does thats sound like my wife, Lloyd?
Indeed yes, but now it doesn't, sorry.
What's up Danna?
I haven't walked out of my office,
not even to pee, in 3 hours.
What are you, agorophobic?
No, I'm scared to see my boss,
because I have no idea what to tell him.
Well that is the beauty of me, Danna,
I tell people what to tell other people.
So tell me something.
Fire Walsh.
- Fire him?
- Yes, I just did.
So he has no intention of writing
what he was supposed to write?
None, but I have intentions
of finding you
an alias writer director
to replace him by sundown
and I will bring him at any cost.
- Get a list together.
- I can't believe this.
Wake up Danna, it's real.
The first big project you brought
in your new studio is in shambles!
Thanks to your writer/director asshole.
You know, if you think my last boss
was vindictive,
you haven't seen shit,
you better find me someone approvable,
and you better make sure
that Vince is on board
because if I have to go in
and tell Richard Wimmer,
that we lost a script, a director,
and a story today,
all of who are your fucking clients,
you can bet your ass that nobody
who has ever been close enough
to smell your breath,
will ever
be welcome at the studio again.
- It's Ari
- I'll call him when I'm finished.
Some help this guy is.
I'm not sleeping jerkoff,
I'm pacing myself.
Yeah, were you enjoying it Turtle?
Yeah, don't get mad, Vin, but,
but I kind of
scanned it for the sex scenes,
There are two good ones,
by the way.
There are a lot of parts in here Vince.
Billy liked the way
you did in Medellin.
- Right?
- No.
I really do need E.
Call him, Turtle.
I can finish man.
Call him.
Call him, Turtle.
Straight to voicemail.
Nice, very nice.
Excuse me miss,
can you make a call for me?
Sure.
Who's the call to?
The call is to Ari Gold,
at the Miller Gold Agency.
And you gonna ask for Lloyd,
and see if
there is anything important going on.
- You got it.
- Thank you very much.
Hey guy.
You are her manager?
Well, can you manage her?
We're ready,
she's not coming out of her trailer.
She's just talking to her boyfriend.
Look, once the sun is over that tree,
we're done, We can't shoot.
Okay, I take care of it.
You wanna talk?
Sorry to bother you, Dave... interrupt.
- But they're ready for all on set.
- We're in the middle of something.
I really have to go.
We'll talk about this later.
What's more important:
this relationship or this photo shoot.
Don't do that, I have to work.
Oh, and I'm sorry, I don't.
- Oh my God.
- Fuck this.
I'm out
I'm really sorry.
He never used to be like this,
but since CW passed on his pilot,.
he's been hanging around my work
beeing all hypercritical.
God, you must think I'm a mess.
Look, relationships are tough,
I'm sure you guys will get trought it.
Does the crew totaly hate me?
Not at all, everyting's fine.
You're good, you need a minute?
No, no, I'm good.
- Okay, here, come on.
- Okay, thank you.
How's that dress feel?
- It's really uncomfortable.
- I agree, right?
You needed me to go
make a phone call for you.
Just confirming,
who I was suppose to call?
You wanna talk to Lloyd
in Ari Gold's office.
If you need to go make
some phone calls, that's fine.
- You're sure?
- Totally.
Alright, I'll be back in 5 minutes.
- Hey, E.?
- Yeah?
I swear I'm not
as a high maintenance as it seems.
Don't worry, as far as my easiest client
are concerned, you're in the top 2.
Not bad!
I'll be back in 2 seconds!
I'm sorry.
So sorry, guys.
Making house calls, I love it.
Today is not the day
to not pick up your phone.
I was reading, you should be proud!
Normally you can't get me to do that.
Well today, I actually
don't need you to do that.
I made some lamb kebabs,
you want some?
- No, thank you.
- They're good.
No, thank you.
You know Richard Kelly?
- The director?
- Yeah, the guy did Donnie Darko.
I know him, I like him, why?
I represent him,
I can get him on Clouds.
Plus I get the studio on board
so we can keep this train rolling.
What about Billy?
Billy is a dead man.
He's a corpse.
You can't pull that kind of shit
when you get paid that kind of money!
Did you read his script?
I understand
that you're loyal to the guy.
But did you read it?
I read the first ten pages
but there's no moutain.
Without a moutain, there's no movie!
No, there is a movie, a great movie,
better than Clouds, I think.
- Are you fucking with me?
- Why would I do that, Ari?
Is he fucking with me?
Clouds was lacking in tits.
This one's got at least 4.
Yeah there is a couple of things
in there for me too.
So you and Lloyd
should get on it ASAP.
Where the hell is E.?
M.I.A.
Well, we need him
because maybe that neurotic little elf
nipping at your heels
will make you understand
that we are in a major
crisis situation here.
I think if you read the script,
you'd find that we're not. Come on.
And Ari, the tide is turning for us,
you know that.
And the hype of Medelin
is growing as Cannes approches,
I like this script,
I wanna make this movie, with Billy.
We can't do that!
There is no way!
There is always a way Ari.
Come on, make it happen, huh?
You're following me Dog?
No, just trying to make a phone call.
Why are you right on my ass?
I'm not, I didn't even know
it was you.
Oh, you didn't?
Okay.
You got a think from my girl?
We work together,
what are you talking about?
- You got a girlfriend?
- No.
- You're gay?
Look at me at my face right now
and tell me
you ain't got a think for my girl.
You gotta chill.
Don't tell me to chill, okay?
My girlfriend, she comes and tells me
she's getting a new manager
I'm thinking it's gonna be
some great beard
Bernie Bernstein type
and not some young
none gay guy who ain't got no girl!
I promise you this relationship
is gonna be nothing but professional.
Professional? How are you
gonna help her professionally?
Why don't you sell me
however you sold her?
I didn't sell her. I told her I didn't
like the movie she was gonna do
and she agreed
with my opinion, that's it.
So you're the reason she didn't do it.
That's fine.
You know that's really fine,
because I was the reason
she was gonna do it!
What can I say about that?
I'm just trying to do that job,
Your job's fucking with my life, okay?
And... you never got me that coke!
This is not happening.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Did you even read Walsh's script?
I read 15 pages
and I will not read another page
nor another page
of any client you ever have.
I need to get you behind this.
I'm not behind this
and I never will be.
Listen, you better get behind this
if you want to save your ass.
Save my ass?
People love Clouds.
I will replace you
and your whole fucking crew,
with 3 phone calls.
And after this if I hear that
you tried to bait and switch the studio,
it will be your ass
that needs the saving.
So you're not gonna take this
to your boss?
- No!
- Then I will.
- Really?
- Hi, Ari Gold to see Richard Wimmer.
Really!
You motherfucking cocksucker.
He's leaving for New York in 30 minutes.
I will be a minute.
No, he's in the shower!
I'm not a fighter Dog. But when
it comes to my girl, I will man up.
So back off, ok?
You're no fighting me man,
you fighting yourself here.
Don't use that weird existential shit
with me.
Would you just talk to me for one second
before you go back over to her?
- One.
- Listen.
One. One.
That was like 3 seconds.
Only 6.
You want to lose your girl?
You go back over there
with that attitude,
that's exactly what will happen.
You'd like that wouldn't you?
What the fuck Dave?
You've come to cause more problems?
Girl, I haven't caused shit!
It's this guy.
The only reason he's here...
is he's trying to fuck you.
- What?
- I'm just trying to do my job!
You need to get rid of him.
Baby, I'm just keeping it real.
Ask him, right now, to look you
in the face and say it isn't so.
- Do it, go on!
- Dave, stop it!
Maybe I should leave.
Yeah, why don't you do that, please?
No, dog, why don't you?
I can't take anymore!
I'm done!
- That shit ain't right.
- Stop talking like Randy Jackson!
Whatever, movie star, I...
I hope you two
are really happy together, alright?
Well...
that was awkard.
You alright?
No, I meant for you...
Okay, come on.
Let's go back to work.
Finally!
Yo, Billy! Where have you been all day?
It's not Billy, Vince. It's Cat.
Billy's locked himself in the bathroom
with a bottle of whisky and a gun.
- What are you talking about?
- He thinks he let you down.
- He feels terrible.
- No, he didn't let me down!
Vince! E.?
Let me talk to him.
Billy? Baby, it's Vince!
He wants to talk to you.
What's to say? I've ruined us all!
No! Baby, he says that it's all good!
What's all good? He liked the script?
Tell him I love the script!
He loved the script, baby. He loved it!
- You loved it?
- It's unbelievable!
You really have a gun?
Yeah, but the bitch
had the bullets all out.
Jesus, Billy!
The script is amazing.
I wanna make this movie.
- You do?
- Yes.
- We're going to make this movie.
- How?
Ari's taking care of it, don't worry.
Ari? What can he do?
Wow, it's like finding
Jim Morrison alive.
Yeah, I had no cell all day.
I got like 25 messages!
- What's going on?
- Nothing that exciting.
Just an emergency meeting
with the head of the studio
on the Billy Walsh/Vinny Chase project.
- What's the problem?
- Would you like to know?
- Ari!
- You snooze, you lose. I gotta go!
- What the hell is going on?
- Desperate times
call for desperate measures here.
Thank God I'm in a robe.
And, may I comment on
what lovely ankles you have!
- Talk fast, Ari.
- You don't have your summer movie?
- Come again?
- At ten poll, you don't have one!
I have Clouds!
Billy Walsh and Vinny Chase
don't wanna do it.
Where the hell is Dana Gordon?
I'm right outside the door, Richard!
Ari locked me out!
Let her in!
- Hey, Dana!
- Fuck you, Ari!
What's the hell's going on with Clouds?
I'm working on it.
When you return from New York,
I'll have
a completely new team in place.
Impossible! Billy burned 6 weeks
writing the wrong script.
And you don't have enough time to put
Clouds back on board
for your July release.
You and your friend Billy Walsh
are dear!
No, we are not dead.
We are very much alive.
You, with your fading star prizes
and your 3 straight quarters in the red
are dead if you're to go
to your board of directors,
and tell them that this summer
may be a worse quarter yet.
I'm gonna tear your head off!
Please don't,
because I have your summer movie.
From the director of Medellin
and Queens Boulevard, comes Silo.
It is the story of a group
of non unionized farmhands
who band together
to survive a nuclear attack
after discovering
an underground society.
It's ready to shoot.
Billy Walsh's on board,
Vinny Chase is on board,
and if you're not,
Fox, Universal and Sony are.
He's bluffing.
What's it matter?
There's a summer movie in there,
we pack up our shit and go home!
Tell him how good it is, Dana.
All personal bullshit aside.
- It's an excellent script.
- Can we market it!
Think... Blade Runner
meets Field of Dreams.
Two classics! Boom!
You make this good, Dana.
And you, Ari, this I don't soon forget.
That was unbelievable.
Blade Runner meets Field of Dreams?
- Not bad, huh?
- You actually read it?
What do we need to read it for?
I'll go to the movies!
We have a gold movie!
Die, Ari! I truly hope you die!
Did I do it, Vinny?
Yes, you did, and thank you.
So... Any possibility of shooting this
a little closer to civilization,
Bill, please?
It takes place on a farm
in Nova Scotia, Turtle.
Ignore him, Billy.
He read every third page.
I, on the other hand, was riveted!
Especially by the character
of Kelton, the farmhand.
Yeah, I was thinking of you
when I wrote that.
- Really?
- No.
How about a toast?
To a groundbreaking day
and a possibly groundbreaking movie!
Are you kissing my ass,
now, snake suit?
Come on, Billy! He came through.
You can't stay mad at him!
Well, I'm no longer planning on
using your car as a toilet,
but I'll get back to you
by being my agent.
I wait with bated breath, Sir!
Why does nobody answer their cells?
Look who's talking!
Where have you been, E.?
Too busy being professional
with your girlfriend
- to pick up the phone?
- Please, tell me what's going on.
Don't stress your pretty little head
about it!
- It's all been handled.
- What's been handled?
We're making Billy's movie.
Silo?
Where is the snow?